theqsweek.com 2016-03-29

# THEQSWEEKONLINE.COM | HOME

**Overview**

The Q S Week (Private) Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and strives to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to this web site. The following statement explains The Q S Week (Private) Limited commitment to managing your personal information and sets out how and when personal information is collected, held, used or disclosed. This Privacy Commitment only applies to data gathered on the theqsweek.com site (the "Web Site"), and does not apply to any other information or web site. 

By registering or by using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Statement. Please read this Statement carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities. If you do not accept the Privacy Statement stated herein or disagree with the way we collect and process personal information collected on the Web site, please do not use it. 

**Scope of this Policy**

This policy applies to www.theqsweek.com (the "Site" or "Web Site"), which is operated and owned by The Q S Week (Private) Limited. It is The Q S Week (Private) Limited's policy to comply with data protection legislation. This regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants you various rights in respect of your personal data. 

The Site contains links to other web sites over which we have no control. The Q S Week (Private) Limited is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

**Information We collect and retain**

You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use this Site or to read the content portions of our Site. We collect the following general types of information during a particular situation about you when you visit our Sites: personal information, demographic information, behavioral information, and indirect information. Sometimes we collect combinations of all these types of information. In each case, it is indicated on the web site whether any personal or demographic data must be provided to use the requested service or not. 

_Personal information_ is information that can be used to identify you, or any other individual to whom the information may relate, personally. We do not collect personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. Some examples of personal information that we collect in some areas of our Site, depending on the services you use and local law, are: 

  * Your name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Contact information
  * Information about third parties, such as references or contacts, that you provide to us if you have their express written consent to do so

**How Information is used**

We use the information we gather on the web site for the purposes of providing our services, responding to any queries you may have, operating and improving the web site, fostering a positive user experience and delivering the products and services that we offer to construction professionals. 

**User's Consent to The Q S Week (Private) Limited to Use the Information**

By registering with The Q S Week (Private) Limited, by managing your profile, or opting in when presented with choices, you have explicitly consented for us to use your information, subject to local law, in the following ways: 

  * to allow you to create an account;
  * to create a profile for you based on information that you have provided to us;
  * to contact you about The Q S Week (Private) Limited Site updates, informational and service-related communications, including important security updates;
  * to provide you additional communications, information, and promotions such as newsletters and other advice;
  * to enable you to provide feedback, to contact us and for us to respond to you;
  * to conduct surveys, questionnaires, promotions and contests, and to provide the results thereof such as success stories and contest winners;

**Updating Account Information**

We wish to ensure your personal information is complete, accurate and up to date. The Q S Week (Private) Limited allows you to change or correct your personal information at any time. To do so, simply log into your My QSWeek account and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted. 

### Important Information

**Security**

You are responsible for ensuring that your log-in credentials (your username and password) are kept confidential. 

**Children**

We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parents. Consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of The Q S Week (Private) Limited, we encourage you to use Web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the Web Site. 

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to materially change the substance of this Privacy Statement, we will, where required, contact you via the email address that you maintain in your profile. We will also post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. 

Thank you for using the Q S Week (Private) Limited. We are committed to providing you with the best tools and advice to help you get ahead in your day to day construction updates. We welcome your feedback and suggestions. Please contact us by calling or email [info@TheQSWeek.com](mailto:info@TheQSWeek.com)

**Legal and Contact Information**

If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to contact us online at [info@TheQSWeek.com](mailto:info@TheQSWeek.com)

We will use reasonable efforts to answer promptly your question or resolve your problem. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact us at [privacystatement@TheQSWeek.com](mailto:privacystatement@TheQSWeek.com)

**Thank you for using The Q S Week (Private) Limited.  
Update effective October, 2012**
